Suck is a comedy, horror, music film directed by Rob Stefaniuk.
The film follows a petty rock band called the Winners, consisting of vocalist Joey Winner, bassist Jennifer, guitarist Tyler, drummer Sam, and French-Canadian
roadie Hugo, along with their sleazy manager Jeff, as they tour across Canada and the USA after Jennifer is turned into a vampire by Queeny.
Meanwhile, a vampire hunter who is afraid of the dark named
Eddie Van Helsing quickly chases them down.
Eddie Van Helsing, played by Malcolm McDowell.
Victor, played by Iggy Pop.
Rockin' Roger, played by Henry Rollins.
Bartender, played by Alice Cooper.
Jennifer, played by Jessica Paré.
Jeff, played by Dave Foley.
Suck is a 2009 vampire black comedy horror film starring,
written and directed by Rob Stefaniuk.
Stefaniuk stars alongside Canadian actress Jessica Paré, Nicole de Boer (Stefaniuk's castmate from the TV series
Catwalk), Malcolm McDowell and rock artists Alice Cooper, Iggy Pop, Henry Rollins and Alex Lifeson of Rush.
Production took place in and around Toronto in late 2008.
The film explores themes of rock 'n' roll, vampire, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.